{
    "id": "b87303221f8240f3a124d742fd5c045e",
    "title": "Should vs. Would",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0d3839cf0ca44ffc83127e6817e3d44e",
            "title": "Would vs. Should",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Alice …………………… arrive soon. She left office at",
                    "description": "We use should to indicate logical possibility.",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………. I carry this bag?",
                    "description": "We use should to ask for a suggestion or to offer help.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Should",
                        "Would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They …………………………. be invited to the party.",
                    "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Everyone ……………………….. abide by the law.",
                    "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You …………………………… waste your time or money.",
                    "description": "Shouldn't can be used to forbid. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "wouldn't",
                        "shouldn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She promised that she ………………………….. help.",
                    "description": "Would is the past tense of will in reported speech.",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………………. be able to come.",
                    "description": "Both would and should can be used with the first person pronouns with little difference of meaning.",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………. you like some more rice?",
                    "description": "We use would in polite offers and requests.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Would",
                        "Should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………. I report this?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Should",
                        "Would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I knew that I …………………………… work harder.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You …………………………….. have told them about my plans.",
                    "description": "Should not have is used to criticize people for doing things. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "shouldn't",
                        "wouldn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ……………………………. have insulted him.",
                    "description": "Should not have is used to criticize people for doing things. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "shouldn't",
                        "wouldn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}